

### **PROFILE**

Adrienne has over 7 years of experience contributing to global ERP implementation projects, across industries and countries, where she applied hey knowledge and know-how in change management and adoption.

Her approach to benefit realisation is to combine the strong theory and Body of Knowledge from **APMG** to clarify the "Why" and "What" of a change initiative; and apply the tools and tactics by **Prosci** to accomplish the "How" (sponsor plan, coaching plan, comms plan, training plan, Resistance management plan)

For the past 4+ years, Adrienne has held two roles on projects: change manager or Training workstream, based on customer requirements. With deliverables that included: Stakeholder engagement, Comms approach, resistance management tactics, training strategy, training delivery.

Adrienne is also a Microsoft Certified professional, with experience on both Dynamics 365 Customer engagement (Sales, Service, Marketing, Field Service) and Finance & Operations.

**FLUENT - WRITING & SPEAKING** 

**English and French** 

# ADRIENNE KUATSE

APMG accredited Change Practitioner, since 2018

# **SOME RECENT DYNAMICS 365 IMPLEMENTATION PROJECTS**

# 1. Manufacturing and Mining sector

Impacted people across the UK , France, Belgium, Germany, America On average ~450 end users per project

# 2. Insurance sector (FinOps & CRM solution)

Impacted people across UK cities
On average ~100 end users per project

#### 3. Public sector

Impacted people across UK cities
On average ~1500 end users per project

# 4. Professional Service Providers

Impacted people across the UK, Spain, Japan, Singapore,

On average ~75 end users per project

### 5. Investment and Wealth Management sector

Impacted people across UK cities On average ~250 end users per project

# 6. Housing Provider sector

Impacted people across UK cities
On average ~750 end users per project

#### 7. Exhibitions and Conference Marketing provider

Impacted people across several countries On average ~100 end users per project

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

Change Management Practitioner course	Accreditation	APMG International
MSc in Logistics and Supply Chain Management	Master	Manchester Metropolitan University (UK)
Development, Monitoring and Evaluation	Diploma	San Sebastian UNESCO Centre (Spain)
MSc in Food Sciences and Nutrition	Master	Ngaoundere University (Cameroon)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **HCL Technologies**

## **Senior Consultant**

2020-To date

On projects, Adrienne owns the Learning & User Adoption/Change workstream depending of the customer requirements. Her remit includes engaging with stakeholder groups across teams/cities/countries to flesh out the impact of the change initiative. Her deliverables include: Resources cost estimates for the change workstream, Comms plan, User Adoption plan, Training strategy, Training delivery & Adoption Evaluation.

### Hitachi Solutions Europe

#### Consultant

2017-2020

Adrienne remit includes engaging with representatives for various stakeholder groups within the business and the project team to produce a Training strategy and a Training plan; as well as, Resources cost estimates for the training and Knowledge transfer workstream and training delivery to Subject Matter Experts, User Acceptance Testers, Business trainers and end-users.

# Bodycote plc

## **ERP Trainer**

2015 - 2017

Within this role, Adrienne facilitated UAT sessions and delivered Training as part of a Dynamics AX2012 global strategic ERP rollout - across UK, France and Belgium; Led the efforts for Curriculum design, role mapping, Training materials creation and translation, delivery and evaluation. Delegates were: End-user, Super user, Finance Director, Manager, Plant Manager, Plant administrator. Speaking French, also meant, I switched to Application Support Team after each go-live.

# Third Sector organisations

### **Trust & Foundation Fundraiser**

2009-2012

Throughout this period Adrienne divided her time between three Manchester-based not-for-profit organisations. Developing, submitting and reporting on Trust & Foundation grants for project bids up to £50,000. In the capacity of a trustee, Adrienne was gathering evidences, establishing the case for support, submitting applications, running the activities within the budget, monitoring & evaluating, writing and submitting end-of-grant report. As a Project Coordinator, I was coordinating the communication between ~40 social workers to ~1000 service users, as well as, between the organisation and all external stakeholders.